****************************************************************
********* Pivotx-SQLite aka Pivotx with SQLite support *********
*********    http://code.google.com/p/pivotx-sqlite/   *********
****************************************************************
Pivotx has a great support for MySQL and a good support for small 'flat-files' based blog, but it lack SQLite. In this fork I'm exploring a way to enable SQLite support, trying to keep the amount of changes as small as possible.

I love pivotx... it's pretty fast, simple and modular. It's template system is easy to understand and it has a smooth learning curve. Over all this, it's GPLed and free both as in free speech as in free beer :P

Pivotx also as a great support for MySQL and a good support for small 'flat-files' based blogs, but unluckily it lack SQLite support.

In this fork I'm exploring a way to add SQLite to Pivotx, trying to keep the amount of changes as small as possible. I'm also trying to not destroy compatibility versus MySQL, even if some parts of original code are really heavily tied... so don't expect this fork to work flawlessy with MySQL.

-== Important disclaimers ==-
***Important disclaimer number 1***
I like Pivotx project, and I don't want steal it any user. If you're happy with your Pivotx setup, if you don't need SQLite support, please, PLEASE use the original Pivotx codebase. Belive me... It rocks. But, if you need SQLite support and you're brave enought, you could try downloading and installing Pivotx-sqlite.

***Important disclaimer number 2***
Please don't ask to official Pivotx forums about problems related to this fork. Ask here first, opening an issue and if it's a original codebase bug I'll repost it to Pivotx forums. 

